export const chapter = "Chapter - 12: Conjunction";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the purpose of Coordinating Conjunctions?",
          optionA: "To introduce subordinate clauses",
          optionB: "To join words or sentences of equal class",
          optionC: "To connect prepositions",
          correctAnswer: "To join words or sentences of equal class",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Identify the Subordinating Conjunction in the sentence: 'Since you have completed the job, you will get your money.'",
          optionA: "Since",
          optionB: "Completed",
          optionC: "You",
          correctAnswer: "Since",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is a set pair of Correlative Conjunctions?",
          optionA: "Either ... or",
          optionB: "Although ... yet",
          optionC: "Both ... but also",
          correctAnswer: "Either ... or",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the correct usage of Correlatives in the sentence: 'She will either sing on the stage or at the backstage.'?",
          optionA: "She will either sing on the stage or at the backstage.",
          optionB: "She will sing on either the stage or at the backstage.",
          optionC: "She will sing either on the stage or at the backstage.",
          correctAnswer:
            "She will either sing on the stage or at the backstage.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which Correlative pair cannot be interchanged with others?",
          optionA: "either ... or",
          optionB: "both ... and",
          optionC: "not only ... but also",
          correctAnswer: "both ... and",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'The train left before the passenger reached the platform,' what type of conjunction is 'before'?",
          optionA: "Coordinating Conjunction",
          optionB: "Subordinating Conjunction",
          optionC: "Correlative Conjunction",
          correctAnswer: "Subordinating Conjunction",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Correct the sentence: 'You may look either for a book or for a diary.'",
          optionA: "You may look either for a book or for a diary.",
          optionB: "You may look for either a book or a diary.",
          optionC: "You may for either a book or a diary.",
          correctAnswer: "You may look for either a book or a diary.",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the purpose of Correlatives in a sentence?",
          optionA: "To introduce subordinate clauses",
          optionB: "To join equal alternatives or parts of a sentence",
          optionC: "To connect prepositions and articles",
          correctAnswer: "To join equal alternatives or parts of a sentence",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Identify the Coordinating Conjunction in the sentence: 'Kavita was going in but Suman was coming out.'",
          optionA: "In",
          optionB: "But",
          optionC: "And",
          correctAnswer: "But",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'He is both clever and intelligent,' what type of conjunction is 'both'?",
          optionA: "Coordinating Conjunction",
          optionB: "Subordinating Conjunction",
          optionC: "Correlative Conjunction",
          correctAnswer: "Coordinating Conjunction",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "1. Coordinating Conjunctions are used to join two words or sentences of ______ class, rank, or order.",
          options: ["a) Different", "b) Superior", "c) Equal"],
          correctAnswer: "c) Equal",
        },
        {
          question:
            "2. A Subordinating Conjunction introduces a subordinate clause and joins it to the principal clause in a sentence, connecting them with words such as ____, ____, or ____.",
          options: [
            "a) and, but, or",
            "b) as, after, before",
            "c) both ... and, not only ... but also",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "b) as, after, before",
        },
        {
          question:
            "3. Correlative Conjunctions occur in pairs, and the first part complements the other part. For example, ____ ... ____.",
          options: [
            "a) although ... yet",
            "b) neither ... nor",
            "c) both ... and",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "c) both ... and",
        },
        {
          question:
            "4. In the sentence 'She will ____ dance on the stage or sing at the backstage,' the correct preposition to fill in the blank is ____.",
          options: ["a) only, in", "b) either, or", "c) not, and"],
          correctAnswer: "b) either, or",
        },
        {
          question:
            "5. The two parts of a Correlative are meant for two alternatives, and the common words that refer to both alternatives must be placed before the ____ part of a Correlative.",
          options: ["a) first", "b) second", "c) neither"],
          correctAnswer: "a) first",
        },
        {
          question:
            "6. The words 'on the' are common to both alternatives in the sentence 'She will dance ____ the stage or on the roof,' but this rule does not apply to ____ and ____.",
          options: [
            "a) before, after",
            "b) prepositions, articles",
            "c) either, or",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "b) prepositions, articles",
        },
        {
          question:
            "7. In the sentence 'You may look ____ a book or ____ a diary,' the correct preposition to fill in both blanks is ____.",
          options: ["a) for, a", "b) either, or", "c) both, and"],
          correctAnswer: "a) for, a",
        },
        {
          question:
            "8. The sentence 'The train left ____ the passenger reached the platform' uses a ____ conjunction.",
          options: [
            "a) before, coordinating",
            "b) after, subordinating",
            "c) although, correlative",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "a) before, coordinating",
        },
        {
          question:
            "9. The preposition typically used with the word 'delight' is ____.",
          options: ["a) on", "b) at", "c) in"],
          correctAnswer: "c) in",
        },
        {
          question:
            "10. The type of combination that gives a particular meaning to some nouns, verbs, or adjectives when used with certain prepositions is called ____.",
          options: ["a) Simile", "b) Metaphor", "c) Phrasal Verbs"],
          correctAnswer: "c) Phrasal Verbs",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Coordinating Conjunctions are used to join words or sentences of equal class, rank, or order.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Subordinating Conjunctions introduce a subordinate clause and join it to the principal clause in a sentence.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Correlative Conjunctions always occur in pairs, and the first part complements the other part.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The sentence 'She will dance either on the stage or at the backstage' demonstrates correct usage of Correlative Conjunctions.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Correlative Conjunctions, the common words that refer to both alternatives must be placed before the second part of the Correlative.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositions and Articles follow the same rule when it comes to their placement in a sentence with Correlative Conjunctions.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The sentence 'You may look either for a book or for a diary' demonstrates correct usage of Prepositions.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The sentence 'The train left before the passenger reached the platform' is an example of a sentence in the Passive voice.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The preposition 'in' is typically used with the adjective 'similar'.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Phrasal Verbs give a particular meaning to some nouns, verbs, or adjectives when used with certain prepositions.",
          options: ["True", "False"],
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
